Personal detail

Nali heights No. 203, Wakanishi 213-5, Kamega, Ikki machi, Aizu-wakamatsu, Fukushima ken, Japan

> +81 50 6868 9169 arevaloarboled@

hotmail.com, gmail.com m5231113@

u-aizu.ac.jp

(7) Git arevaloarboled

in Linkedin

ArevaloCamilo

uan Camilo Arévalo Arboleda

Curriculum Vitae

Rersonal profile

I have a bachelor in computer science with experience in animation, interactive systems, and web-oriented computation. I am mainly interested in music information retrieval, speech recognition, web back-end development, VR development, software development, machine learning, and data mining. I am disciplined, proactive, responsible, acquisitive and with excellent analytic skills. I stand out for excellent performance in programming code.

Education

Currently – 04/2019 Master Student in Computer Science

Research topic: Sound spatialisation

GPA 4.0/4.0

11/2018 - 07/2012 **Bachelor of Computer Science** Pontifical Xavierian University Cali

Cum Laude, GPA 3.81/5

Program with ABET international accreditation

</> Programming

LISP

PHP

PYTHON



Experience

Currently - 04/2019 Teacher Assistant

Assist in the practical and theoretical lectures of computer science undergrad-

University of Aizu

University of Aizu

uate courses. Sush as: Virtual reality, Sound and audio processing and C++ programming. Tasks: preparing material, solve doubts and grading exercise.

12/2018 - 06/2018

Research Assistant

Pontifical Xavierian University Cali

Built an online game "Tramas: parques intercultural," as a didactic tool to promote the intercultural dialogue.

11/2018

RUBY

Internship

University Complutense of Madrid

Researched and implemented a tracking map for artworks of artistic heritage value during the Spanish civil war and the postwar.

08/2016 - 06/2016

Research Assistant

Pontifical Xavierian University Cali

Developed an digital representation of Spanish pieces of art for historical re-

search.

X Frameworks 12/2014 - 08/2014

and tools **Pure Data**

SQL

Years of experience

Research Assistant

Pontifical Xavierian University Cali

Researched, designed, and implemented an algorithm capable of finding salsa song choruses for the construction of a data set.

Unity **MATLAB Arduino Boostrap &**

AngularJS OpenMPI/OpenMP

Spanish

English

April 3, 2020

OpenCV **NodeJS** Docker

Publications

Accurate Spatialization of VR Sound Sources in the Near Field.

[Undergraduate thesis]

Camilo Arévalo, Gerardo M. Sarria M., Julián Villegas.

AES Int. Con. on Spatial Reproduction - Aesthetics and Science (Tokyo, Japan) 2018.

OO Developing a Narrative Database for Spanish Art Starting from the End.

A.A. Navarro Newball, I. Moreno Sánchez, B. Barinaga López, D.F. Loaiza, L.S. Osorio, F.D. Paredes, J. C. Arévalo, S. Juri, E.M. Amézquita, V.E. Contreras.

Languages 12th Colombian Conference on Computing (12CCC), Cali, Colombia 2017.

(Native) Towards an Efficient Algorithm to Get the Chorus of a Salsa Song. (Fluent)

Camilo Arévalo, Gerardo M. Sarria M., Mario Mora, Carlos Arce-Lopera.

Japanese (Conversational) IEEE International Symposium on Multimedia (ISM2015), Miami, FL, USA 2015.



Honors & awards

3rd prize in Expo poster REDIS South West Node 2018

Research graduation contest held by 21 undergraduate Computer Science programs insti-

DBMS 2016 **Relational DB**

Ranked 8th in the ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) South America / North Regional 2016 Member of "CodeBreakers" team

2015 Ranked 20th in the ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) South America / North Regional 2015

Member of "CodeBreakers" team

2014 Honorable mention in the ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) South America / North Regional 2014

Member of "CodeBreakers" team

2013 Ranked 24th in the ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) South America / North Regional 2013

Member of "CodeBreakers" team

